reelworldfilmfest.com 2015-05-31

# Privacy

ReelWorld Film Festival is committed to protecting the privacy of everyone who visits the ReelWorld Film Festival website (www.reelworld.ca). Our Privacy Policy below outlines what personal information we collect from the website, how/if we use that information and whom/if we share it.

ReelWorld respects all of the website’s visitors’ privacy. We do not sell, give or exchange any of the information we collect from the site to any individual/company/organization outside of ReelWorld.

We do use the information collected from our website in the following ways:

  * To communicate with you. After joining our mailing list, you may receive newsletters, promotions and invitations from ReelWorld. In order to distribute this information, ReelWorld collects the subscribers’ email addresses. We do not share these emails with any individuals/groups/companies outside of ReelWorld. You may unsubscribe from the ReelWorld email list at anytime by sending an email to: info(at)reelworld.ca, subject headline: unsubscribe from mailing list.
  * To administer submissions and applications to our Festival, programs and events.
  * To assist you if you have any questions or suggestions.

Disclosure Required by Law

If circumstances arise wherein ReelWorld is compelled by law, court order, subpoena or other legal compulsion to disclose website users’ personal information to a government authority or a third party, ReelWorld will comply with all such legal obligations.

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy or the use of your personal information, please contact ReelWorld directly at info(at)ReelWorld.ca
